〈（薫）夏休みを利用して
バス旅行に出かけた私と純一は〉
Junichi and I left for a bus tour during summer break.
〈二人してハシャギすぎたせいで
天罰が下ったのか〉
Maybe we received divine punishment for being too excited,
〈サービスエリアに
置いていかれてしまったのです〉
but we were left behind in a service area.
（純一）やっぱり　うな茶セットなんて
食べてる場合じゃなかったんだ
I knew we shouldn't have had that eel and tea set.
（薫）じゃ　私のせいだって言うの？
純一だって食べたじゃない
Are you saying it's my fault?
それは　そうだけど…
何よ　私のせいにしないでよ！
You had the set too.
I did, but...
してないだろッ
してるわよ！
What? Stop pushing the responsibility onto me!
I'm not!
（クラクション）
You are!
〈でも　その時はまだ二人とも〉
〈これから自分達の身に
どんなことが起こるのかを〉
However, the two of us could never
have imagined what was in store for us.
〈想像することさえ
できませんでした〉
出逢った瞬間
Deatta shunkan
From the moment we met
感じてた運命を 確信に変えたくて
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
SS
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
SS
＋
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
今日も 君の傍に居るのかな
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
君の全てに
Kimi no subete ni
Everything about you
Check My Soul
ハートが動き出した
Haato ga ugokidashita
My heart begins to wake
今君と一緒に駆け出そう
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Let's break into a run together right now
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
夢のような空間の中でも
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
Even in dreamlike moments
真実だけを見つめていたい
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
I only want to gaze at the truth
瞳の奥の
Hitomi no oku no
Inside your eyes
Check My Soul
（運転手）そりゃ災難だったな
はい
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
まさか置いていかれるなんて
思ってもみなかったので
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
薫は限定品とか　ご当地って言葉に
弱すぎるんだよ
まだ　言うの？　自分だって食べて
よかったって言ってたくせに
そりゃそうは思ったよ　でも
薫が時間を勘違いしてるなんて
That's some hard luck.
Yes, we had no idea we'd be left behind.
思ってもみなかったから
違ってるかもって思ってたんなら
Kaoru, you're way too weak towards
limited-time items and local delicacies.
まずいんじゃないって　もっと強く
言ってくれればよかったじゃない
You're still harping on about that?
You said yourself that you were glad you had some!
薫が凄く食べたそうにしてたから
私ばっかり責めないでよ
I did think that.
誰も責めたりしてないじゃないか
ほら　その言い方がそうでしょ
But that was because I didn't think that you'd have your times wrong.
それっくらいにしといたら　どうだ
まったく絵に描いたみてえだな
If you figured that I had it wrong, then you
should've been more insistent in telling me.
何がですか？
よく言うじゃねえか
Well, you looked like you really wanted to try it.
ケンカするほど仲がいいって
あ…
Stop putting all the blame on me!
I'm not even blaming you or anything!
まあ　とりあえず
さっき話したとおり　この先の
Listen to the tone of your voice.
駅まで乗せてくから
That's about enough arguing, don't you think?
すみません
申し訳ないです
You guys would make the perfect example.
Huh?
Of what?
ああ　確か
駅のそばに温泉宿があったから
Don't you know of this phrase?
"To love each other enough to have arguments".
今夜は　そこに
泊まればいいんじゃないか？
温泉！？
いわゆる　山里の温泉って感じでな
Anyway, like I said before, I'll
drive you to nearest train station.
ひなびた　いい感じなんだ　これが
Sorry.
へえ
温泉…
I apologize.
Tanamachi Kaoru
2nd Half
Companion
I recall there being a hot spring inn by the
train station, so you can stay there for the night.
《あ…》
Hot spring?!
I believe it's like some mountain hot spring.
《ああ…》
It's a nice place in the countryside, it is.
《ねえ　純一　湯加減はどう？》
I see.
Hot spring...
Hey, Junichi.
How does the water feel?
《いい…》
Nice...
Very nice!
凄く　いい～！
わああ～！
純一
あッ？
Junichi.
What's wrong?
どうかしたの？
いやあ　別に
Nah, it's nothing.
そんなにいいんなら　決まりだな
そうですよね
I guess it's decided if you're that excited about it.
Y-Yeah.
まあ　それにしても良かったな
二人旅で
But man, it must be nice to go on a trip with your partner.
えッ？
旅は道連れ世は情けっちゅうだろ
Don't you know of the saying, "companions for trips and compassion for the world"?
はあ
旅には
Yeah.
Just like how it's reassuring to have a companion on a trip,
連れがいる方が心強いように
世の中渡っていくには
having the compassion to support each other in the journey of life is also important.
お互いに支え合う
人情が大切なんだよな
Thank you so much.
本当にありがとうございました
助かりました
You really helped us out.
See ya. Don't have too many arguments!
じゃあな　あんまケンカすんなよな
（クラクション）
What a nice person.
いい人だったわね
そうだな
Yeah.
This is the hot spring inn he recommended, right?
さてと　オススメの温泉旅館は
こっちの方よね？
Old Dragon God Hot Springs
本当に　ここなのか？
たぶん　そのはずなんだけど…
Is this really the place?
I think so...
Let's check it out.
じゃあ行ってみるか
う　うん
Y-Yeah.
どうした？
へッ？
What's wrong?
Are you scared?
もしかして怖いのか？
こんなの怖いわけないじゃない
Wh-Why would I be scared?
ふーん
（小枝を踏む）
Kaoru?
薫！？
えッ　ああッ
I-It's nothing!
別に
ふーん
思いっきり驚いたよな？　今
That totally scared you, didn't it?
遊園地のアトラクションとかは
平気なくせに
You're totally fine with the rides in amusement parks, but you're actually scared of this stuff?
もしかして薫　怖いのか？
べッ　別に
怖がってなんかないんだから
I-It's not like I'm not scared or anything!
I was just pretending to be surprised.
ちょっと驚いたふりしただけよ
≪（女将）あの…
Um...
（２人）うわ～ッ！
Go ahead and take a bath if you'd like.
≪（女将）
よろしければ　お風呂どうぞ→
It's a natural hot spring.
天然温泉なんですよ
（２人）はあ…
本日お泊まりのお客様は
お二人だけなので
You two are the only customers here tonight, so take your time and enjoy.
ごゆっくりどうぞ
はあ
はあ…
This place is kinda creepy.
何か　薄気味悪い所ね
そうだな
Yeah.
えッ　どこ行くの？
ちょっと　トイレ
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
えーッ！
何だよ？
What?
私も行くわよ
はあ？
I-I'm going too.
あッ　もしかして薫
１人になるのが怖いんだろ？
Don't tell me you're scared of being left alone?
That's not it!
そんなことないわよ
ふふん　怖いくせに
だから違うってば
You're obviously scared.
I said I'm not!
一緒についてってあげるのよ
はいはい
I'm just doing you a favor by going with you!
Right.
こっちかな？
そうじゃないかしら
Is it over here?
I guess not...
何やってるんだよ？
えッ？
What are you doing?
どうして
僕の背中に張りついてるんだ？
Why are you stuck to my back?
そう見えた？
純一の気のせいじゃない？
You... You think so?
Aren't you just imagining things?
はいはい
Right.
What was that sound?
今の音　何？
さあ
No idea.
Junichi, go take a look.
純一　見てきてよ
ええッ　しょうがないな
I guess I can...
じゃあ　ここにいろよ
ま…　待って　やっぱり私も行く
You stay here, then.
W-Wait, I'll go with you, after all.
あああ…
うわーッ
Is something the matter?
≪（女将）どうかなさいましたか？
あッ…？
うん？
あッ
あッ！
お食事こしらえてますので
先に　お風呂どうぞ
Your meal is being prepared,
so feel free to take a bath first.
O-Okay.
はッ　はい！
Female
Male
じゃあ　後で
ああ
Well, see you in a bit.
Yeah.
ねえ　先に部屋に帰らないで
ここで待っててよ
Hey, don't go back to the room
without me. Wait for me here, okay?
ああ　分かったよ
Yeah, I won't.
薫　怖がりだな
誰が怖がりだって！？
Kaoru's a scaredy-cat.
Who are you calling a scaredy-cat?!
雰囲気出てるなあ
This place has a nice feel to it.
きゃー！
薫！　どうした？
Kaoru, what's wrong?!
今　そこに何かいたよう…　な…
Something seemed to be there just... now...
な？
いやあ　出てけ　変態！
Now?
Get out, you pervert!
Sorry!
ごめん！
うわあ　待って　行かないで
Wait, don't go!
隅っこの方になら
入ってていいわよ
I don't mind if you take the corner.
ねえ　純一
Hey, Junichi.
こっちに…
Come...
What?!
何？
あー　こら　猿！　私のブラ返せッ
Hey, monkey!
Give me my bra back!
えッ？
うん？　あ…
純一のバカー！
わあ！
Junichi, you idiot!
ふう　さんざんだったな
もう　あの猿！
That sucked.
Damn that monkey!
あれ　お気に入りだったのに
That was one of my favorites, too...
あッ！
わあ　凄いごちそう
Wow, what a feast!
では　ごゆっくり
Please enjoy.
I'm digging in!
いっただっきまーす
何から食べようかしら
What should I start off with?
うふ　幸せ
って　いきなり上機嫌か？
I'm so happy!
Why are you suddenly in such a good mood?
だって　おいしいんだもん
It tastes really good, you know!
ごちそうさま　うーん　満腹満腹
Thanks for the food.
Mmh, I'm so full!
おなかいっぱいになったら
急に眠くなってきちゃったわね
Having a full stomach makes you kinda sleepy.
えッ…
どうした？　薫
What's wrong, Kaoru?
あッ
ねえ　純一
うん？
Hey, Junichi.
I can't make up my mind on something.
私ね　ちょっと迷ってたのよね
何を？
On what?
How to approach our relationship.
純一と　どうつきあっていけば
いいのかなって
It's getting harder for me to tell where the
line between being friends and being lovers is.
何か
友達と恋人の境界線みたいなのが
よく分かんなくなっちゃったの
だから今回の旅行で
That's why I was hoping to clear it up by going on this trip.
確かめられたらいいかなって
思ってたんだけど
But this ended up happening...
何か　こんなことになっちゃって…
純一？
Junichi?
Good night.
おやすみ
Huh?
あれ？
どうしたの？
What's wrong?
いや　財布が…
えッ？
No, my coin purse...
とりあえず私が払っておくわね
ああ　ごめん
I'll pay for now.
Sorry.
よろしければ
またいらしてくださいね
Please come again.
Did you find your coin purse?
で　お財布はあった？
それが…
Well...
えッ？
No way!
ウソ！
公衆電話に置き忘れたってこと？
Did you leave it behind at the public phone?
Yeah.
ああ　あの時　焦ってたから
I was panicking at the time, so...
どうすんのよ？　さっきの支払いで
Now what? I barely have any money left from paying the inn fees.
私のお金も
もう　ほとんど残ってないわよ
ごめん
もう　こんなことになるなら
Sorry.
If I knew this'd happen, I would've walked all the way to the station last night and waited for the first train.
昨日の晩のうちに駅まで行って
始発電車待った方が良かったわよ
その時は財布がないなんて
気づかなかったんだから
I didn't realize I left my coin purse behind at the time, you know.
仕方ない　薫だっていけないんだぞ
どうして？
I mean, it's partly your fault too.
How come?!
サービスエリアで　お菓子を買いすぎて
無駄遣いしたじゃないか
You wasted money buying way too many snacks at the service area.
How is that wasting money?
無駄遣いじゃないわよ
限定品との出会いは…
Coming across limited-time items is...
一期一会って言いたいんだろ
それは　もう聞き飽きたよ
..."like a once-in-a-lifetime encounter", right?
I'm sick of hearing that!
もういい！
あッ…
Whatever!
Which path did we come from?
どっちから来たんだっけ？　なあ薫
Hey, Kaoru...
薫　そっちなのか？
私の勘よ
Kaoru, we came that way?
I'm just going by my instinct.
Instinct?
勘って…　間違ってたら
どうするつもりなんだ？
What'll we do if you're wrong?
じゃあ　純一は　そっち行ったら？
ああ　おい…
You can go take the other path, then.
勝手にしろ！
Have it your way!
This really is the wrong path...
やっぱり　こっちじゃなかった…
あッ　待てよ　わあッ…
Wait-
純一？
イテテテ
Junichi?
Ow...
Are you okay, Junichi?
大丈夫？　純一
ああ
Yeah, I'm fine.
平気　平気
あッ　あれ！
Over there!
Old Dragon God
Central Bus
Thank goodness there's a bus stop here.
こんなところにバス停があって
助かったよ
Right, Kaoru?
なあ　薫　あ…
そうね
Yeah.
うわッ
Damn that monkey!
《もう　あの猿！
あれ　お気に入りだったのに》
That was one of my favorites, too...
うん？
うわッ
What's wrong?
どうかした？
いやあ　その
No, uh...
いえ　見てません　いや　見ました
じゃなくて
No, I didn't see anything!
Old Dragon God
Central Bus
I mean, I did!
No, I didn't see anything important!
大事なところは見てません
純一のバカ！
Junichi, you idiot!
Old Dragon God
Central Bus
イッタイ…　前にも
こんなことがあったような
That hurt.
I get the feeling this happened before.
前にもって　女に
叩かれるようなことしたの？
Before? You did something to make a girl slap you?
It's just a feeling.
気がしただけです
フフフ…
何だよ　いきなり笑って失礼だな
だって　ほっぺに手形が
What? That's not nice of you to suddenly laugh.
But there's this hand mark on your face...
えッ　あッ　何　手形が残るくらい
強く叩いてんだよ！？
You slapped me hard enough to leave a hand mark?!
I'm sorry!
ごめん　ごめん
（笑い続ける薫）
当たりだったな
えッ？
You were right.
薫の勘　バス停があったじゃないか
Your instinct. We managed to find a bus stop.
ごめんね
えッ？
Sorry.
何か私　ひどいことばっかり言って
I kept saying horrible things and blaming you...
純一のこと責めてばっかで
いや　財布なくしたの僕だから
Well, I did lose my coin purse.
ううん　うな茶セット食べたいって
言い張ったのは私だし
Nah, I was the one who insisted on having the eel and tea set.
それに　純一が言ったとおり
限定品のお菓子買いすぎたと思う
And like you said, I guess I do buy too many limited-time snacks.
That's not true.
そんなことない　僕も言いすぎたよ
I went too far myself.
本当に　ごめんなさい
I'm really sorry.
Me too.
僕の方こそ
Sorry.
ごめん
なあ　薫
うん？
Hey, Kaoru.
We're still in the middle of our trip, so let's have fun from now on.
まだ旅は途中なんだし
これからは楽しくやっていこう
Let's have the rain wash away what's happened so far.
今までのことは
この雨の水に流そう
うまいこと言うわね
That's pretty poetic.
あッ
やんだな
やんだわね
It stopped.
It did.
Excuse me, but this bus stop isn't in use anymore.
お二人さん　このバス停は
もう使っとらんからな
バスは来んよ
（２人）えッ？
There's no bus coming.
（２人）えーッ！
小銭　これしかないから
分かった
This is all the change I have left.
Got it.
（呼び出し中）
[TEL]（美也）はい　橘です
もしもし　美也か？
Hello, this is Tachibana.
Hello, Miya?
[TEL]あッ　にぃに？　えっとね今朝
バス会社の人から電話あってね
Oh, it's you, Nii-nii?
Miya, truth is-
Someone from the bus company called this morning.
[TEL]何か分かんないけど「スミマセン」って
言ってた　荷物預かってるって
I don't really know why, but he apologized and said he'd hold your luggage for you.
[TEL]にぃに　荷物なくしたの？
でもね　みゃー
Did you lose your stuff?
Well, about that-
I'll be paying to have it delivered back home, so don't worry.
[TEL]着払いで家に送ってもらう
ようにしておいたから大丈夫
I'm so considerate, right?
[TEL]みゃー　気が利くでしょう
そうか　あのな…
I see. But you know-
So there's no need to worry at all.
[TEL]全然　心配ないからね
少し黙っ…
Miya, stop talking for a s-
By the way, Nii-nii, where are you?
[TEL]ところで　今どこにいるの？
だから…
I'm trying t-
あッ…
純一？
Junichi?
切れた
I got cut.
交番でも探すか
そうね
We should look for a police box.
Yeah.
薫？
Kaoru?
でも　せっかくだから　もう少し
ここで遊んでいきましょう
But since we're here anyway, let's play around for a little longer.
あッ
純一　早く！
Junichi, come on!
（純一・薫）ハア　ハア　ハア　ハア…
Hey, Junichi.
ねえ　純一
うん？
今回のことで
分かったことがあるの
I learned something from all this.
えッ？
何だかんだいっても私
I learned that I really do have a lot of fun when I'm with you, after all.
純一と一緒にいると
すっごく楽しいってこと
それは僕も同じだ
That's true for me, too.
Let's continue to get along.
これからも　よろしくね
僕の方こそ
My sentiments as well.
Hey!
≪（梅原）おーい！
（梅原）おーい！
Hey!
おーい
大将！　棚町！
Boss! Tanamachi!
梅原　どうしてここに？　あッ！
What's Umehara doing here?
《この夏は俺は寿司修業
大将は男修業か》
This summer, I'll be on sushi training and you'll be on man training, huh?
《頑張れよな》
Work hard at it!
そうか
男修業は　うまくいってんのかー？
I see.
Is the man training going well?
上々だ！
くー　うらやましいね　大将！
It's going awesome!
I'm so jealous of you, boss!
俺も頑張るぞ
I'll double my efforts!
助かった　助かったぞ　薫！
We're saved.
We're saved, Kaoru!
えッ？
まさに地獄に仏だ
It's like Buddha's come to save us from hell!
〈こうして　私と純一の旅は
何とか終わりました〉
And that was how my trip with Junichi ended.
My very last high school summer break turned out to be amazing.
〈そして
この高校生活　最後の夏休みは〉
〈私にとって
最高の夏休みになったんです〉
グッモ～
Good morn'!
（恵子）あッ　薫　おはよう
橘君なら　まだだよ
Morning, Kaoru.
Tachibana-kun hasn't arrived yet.
恵子に用事があったから来たのよ
またそんなこと言って
I'm looking for you.
This again?
いいのいいの　分かってるから
ホントよ　恵子に話があって
It's okay, I know what you mean.
No seriously, I'm looking for you.
もう旅行の話なら　夏休み中
さんざん電話で聞いたから
If it's about the trip, you've already told me plenty about it over the phone during summer break.
もういいよ　ごちそうさま
ううん
It's enough for me. I enjoyed it.
No, I wanted to thank you face-to-face.
ちゃんと顔を見て
お礼が言いたかったの
Thank you, Keiko.
ありがとう恵子
えッ　何？
Huh? What?
私に旅行をすすめてくれたこと
ホントにありがとう
Thank you so much for suggesting that I go on a trip.
凄く　いい思い出になったわ
I made some really good memories.
そう　良かった
I see. That's good.
おはよう
うっす！
Morning.
Sup.
Morning, Junichi.
おはよう　純一
はい　これ　仕上げといたわよ
Here, I fixed this up for you.
Thank you.
サンキュー
わあッ！
わあ～
どう？　いいでしょ
ああ
Well? Nice, isn't it?
Yeah.
≪（恵子）
いいな　宿題手伝ってもらって
You're so lucky to get help with your homework.
≪（梅原）ずるいぞ　大将
ありがとうな
No fair, boss.
Thanks.
ううん　いいのよ
あッ　灯台描くの忘れてた
No problem.
Oh no, I forgot to draw the lighthouse.
ちょっと失礼
えッ　あッ　おい　ちょ…
Excuse me.
Hey, wait...
薫　何してんだよ！？
何って
Kaoru, what are you doing?!
Huh?
絵を直すのに決まってるじゃない
いやあ　そういうことじゃなくて
I'm fixing the drawing for you, obviously.
No, that's not what I meant...
じゃあ　どういうことよ？
いやあ　だから…
What is it, then?
Well, like...
気にしない　気にしない
これが私と純一なんだから
It's nothing to worry about.
This is how you and I are.
だな
Yeah.
朝を運ぶバイクの音が
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
僕に時間の流れ告げ
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
もうどこへも行けない気持ち
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
君に渡す覚悟決めた
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
未来に散りばめた 予定は隣に 君がいてほしい
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
息を吸って吐き出す
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
言葉は幾度もため息に変わるけど
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
伝えたい言葉はただひとつだけ
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
好きだよ
Suki da yo
"I love you"
僕の告白
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
≪夏休みも　もう終わり
時間がたつのは早いよね
Preview
Next episode preview.
Summer break ended already.
（梅原）光陰矢の如しとは
よく言ったもんだよな
Time passes really quickly, doesn't it?
They say that time flies like an arrow, don't they?
≪そういえば梅原君
寿司修業に行ってたんだよね
Hey, wait-
Oh by the way, Umehara-kun.
Didn't you go on sushi training?
（梅原）この夏俺は
寿司職人の階段を１段上ったぜ
Yeah. I've taken the first step in
my quest to become a sushi chef!
≪大人の階段も
寿司職人の階段も同じだよね→
The quest to become an adult is the same
as the quest to become a sushi chef, right?
１段ずつ着実に上らないと
何だよ　それ？
You have to take it one step at a time!
≪橘君いたんだ
（梅原）大将　ボヤボヤするなよ
What the heck's that?
Oh, I didn't know you were here, Tachibana-kun.
お前ら！
You should perk up, boss.
You guys are unbelievable!
≪そういえば
ナレーションのあの人は…？
Next Episode
Nakata Sae
1st Half
Next Episode
Nakata Sae
1st Half
Next Episode
Nakata Sae
1st Half
Doubt
Next episode: "Doubt".
By the way, who was supposed to be narrating?